老兄 看看我们一下午的杰作
Dude, check out what we've been working on all afternoon.
打节奏 嗯哼!
Hit it, b. Unh!
接着
Takin' it
嗯!
Unh!
双人跳 开始!
Double Dutch. Go!
啊!
Unh!
好 看完了 接下来
Okay, now that that's settled, what are we doing
这半天 我们做什么?
with the rest of our day?
在电视上看"菜鸟大反攻"马拉松赛
"Revenge of the Nerds" marathon on basic cable.
好吧 我知道自己在接下来七个小时要干什么
Sweet. I know what I'm doing with the next seven hours.
是啊 我知道你一边玩"菜鸟大反攻III"
Yeah, I heard if you play "revenge of the nerds III"
一边听TLC的"疯狂性感酷"
and TLC'S "crazy sexy cool" at the same time,
这两个的组合这是太给力了
they sync perfectly.
抱歉 兄弟们 我不能陪你们玩了
Sorry. Can't join you guys.
我和简有个坑爹的双重约会
Me and Jane have an awesome double date planned.
我们在一个酒吧见面 可能会谈些...
We're gonna hit a wine bar, probably talk about...
-好的学区-你是想跟我们待一起的 对吗?
- good school districts. - You wanna stay here, don't ya?
我当然想了! 拉马是
Of course I do! Lamar is, like,
是最著名的美国黑人电影
the third most influential African-American character
除了真情电波和马尔科姆·艾克斯
in movie history after Radio and Malcolm X.
都不许动
Nobody move!
我上个星期剩下来的鸡肉三明治不见了
My leftover chicken parm sando from last week is missing,
我想知道谁拿了
and I want answers.
戴夫 你知道我有多重视我的下午茶的
Dave, you know how seriously I take my predinner meal.
马克斯 你怎么不直接承认你吃了两顿晚餐?
Max, why don't you just admit that you eat two dinners?
我又不是霍比特人
Because I'm not a hobbit.
霍比特人吃两顿早饭
Hobbits ate two breakfasts.
是的 他们就是这样的
He does that, too.
不要转移话题! 关键是我的吃的不见了
That's not the point! The point is that food is missing,
这不是第一次了
and this is not the first time.
一星期前 我的碎肉玉米煎饼没了
My carnitas burrito from a week ago... gone.
上个星期三 我的肉披萨...噗的一声!
My meat-pocalypse pizza from last Wednesday... poof!
消失在空气中 我的四十八块炸鸡
Into thin air. My 48-piece chicken nugget that
准备留着过生日吃的 也不见了!
I was saving for my birthday has just vanished!
老兄 你疯了吧
Dude, you're acting crazy.
是吗? 我疯了吗? 我疯了?!
Am I? Am I? Am I?!
嗯!
Unh!
哈!
来谈谈!
Talk about it!
别试图用跳舞来缓和气氛
Don't ease the tension with dance.
幸福终点站
第一季第三集
==深影字幕组==
简 真不敢相信
Jane, I can't believe
你从来没泡过巴克顿的韩国温泉
you've never been to that Korean spa in Bucktown.
人家也不敢相信呢
I can't either.
不过我假装每家温泉都去过了
I thought I'd been to every spa imaginable.
那里还能搓澡
This place does an akasuri face scrub.
真是天上人间啊
That is life-changing.
比四季酒店的鲍鱼海藻面膜还好?
Better than the abalone sea kelp wrap at the four seasons?
嘿 布拉德 你知不知道她们在说什么
Hey, Brad, do you have any idea what these two are talking about right now?
当然知道啊 磨砂可以给你的脸去死皮
Oh, yeah. See, a scrub can really exfoliate your face,
但是敷面膜...让我来跟你好好说说...
but a wrap... now that just gets in th...
不 完全不知道她们在说啥
Nope. No clue.
我喜欢啤酒 老兄 还有响尾蛇
I like beer, man, and rattlesnakes.
简 我有一些免费的温泉门票
Jane, I have some free spa passes.
我想邀请你和我一起去
I'd love for you to go with me as my guest.
太给力了
I would love that.
好极了 布拉德 你们男同志就去外面逛逛
Good. Brad, you guys could hang out
看看比赛神马的
and watch the game
我们去泡泡温泉 是不是很棒?
while we go to the spa. Wouldn't that be great?
耶 没错 真是好极了!
Yeah. Yeah, that'd be awesome.
-你真是太坑爹了!-我就知道你会这么说的
- That's gonna be horrible! - I knew you were gonna say that.
你说话的声音会变尖
Your voice as gets so high
-当你不喜欢做什么事的时候 -什么?
- when you don't wanna do something. - What?
"我喜欢豆腐烧排骨"
"I love tofu spareribs."
"当然了 我会和岳父岳母去葡萄酒之乡的"
"Sure, I'll go to wine country with your parents."
"完事之后我会好好照顾你的"
"I'll totally take care of you after you finish with me."
我才没有捏 不管怎么说
I don't do that. Whatever.
听着 我跟卡尔共事
Look, I work with Carl,
但是我可不想跟他成为朋友
but I don't wanna be friends with him.
我们的朋友已经够多了
We have enough friends.
布拉德 我们谈过这个的
Brad, we've talked about this.
你得学着接受新事物 要勇于创新
You need to be open to new things, new experiences.
我有创新啊
I'm open to new experiences.
在过去的十五年里 你都穿一样的万圣节礼服
You've worn the same Halloween costume for the past 15 years.
我喜欢!
I love it!
Jane穿的是著名的Lady gaga 2009年参加VMA颁奖礼时的蒙面蕾丝装
双人斯努基!
Double Snookis!
呜 呜 呜 呜
Woof, woof, woof, woof,
呜 呜! 看我的新造型
woof, woof! There's my fresh, fly posse!
哦 来吧! 我的恶狗帮在哪里?
Oh, yes! Where my dog pound at?
我的恶狗帮在哪里? 好啊!
Where my dog pound? Yes!
你在说什么呢? 阿瑟尼奥超经典的
What are you talking about? Arsenio's timeless.
听着 我真的很喜欢卡尔和戴安娜
Look, I really like Carl and Dianne.
他们很有经验 因为他们比我们结婚久多了
They're sophisticated. They've been married longer.
我们可以向他们学习的
We could really learn from them.
好吧
Fine.
我会和卡尔继续见面的
I'll go on a dude date with Carl,
但是我想做一次海藻面膜
but I want one of those sea kelp face wraps.
人家喜欢T字部位都水润润的~
You know I like my "T" zone all supple and dewy.
见鬼 怎么一下子性奋了起来?
Damn it. Why does that turn me on?
嗯~
Mm.
今晚这小帅哥可真多啊 阿历
Lot of cute guys here tonight, Al.
嗯 我还不想钓男人 彭
Eh, not really what I'm looking for, Pen.
不清楚 你和戴夫分居一段时间了
I don't know. It's been a while since you and Dave split up.
我是说 或许你该开始约会了
I mean, maybe you should think about dating again.
我还是觉得我没有准备好
I still don't think I'm ready yet.
嗯哼 你确定吗? 我觉得今晚
Mm. Are you sure? Because I feel like tonight would be
你该试一试了 立刻马上
the perfect night for you to get back out there, like, now.
我不觉得
I don't think so.
好吧 如果你困在了森林的陷阱里面
Okay, well, what if you were stuck in a trap in the woods
一只狮子准备吃你...那你会出去约会吗?
and, like, a cougar was trying to eat you... would you date then?
真是太不可理喻了 怎么可能发生那种事?
That's insane. Why would that even happen?
我不知道 忽略掉 因为你爸爸
I have no idea. Forget that. 'Cause maybe your dad is
是反恐精英 他只有
the head of some elite counterterrorist unit. He only
只有二十四小时可活了...
has 24 hours to...
算了吧! 关键是 你到底要不要去约会?
I don't know! The point is, would you date?
-嗯 是的 -我就知道!
- Uh, yes. - I knew it!
嗨 美女们 我是克拉克 这位是皮特
Hi. I'm Clark. This is Pete.
双人约会 大惊喜!
Surprise double date!
服务员 来点茴香酒 不用谢
Waiter, round of sambucs. You're welcome.
你能相信彭妮跟我一起搞双人约会
Can you believe Penny surprise double dated me?
我是说 那感觉就像参加
I mean, I feel like I was
江苏卫视的非诚勿扰一样
on a UPN reality show.
太疯狂了
Crazy.
好吧 马克斯我叫你来是要你帮我粉墙的
Okay, Max, I hired you to help me paint the store,
不是让你躺着的
okay, not lay around.
好吧 那你为什么要把这些报纸都铺在地上?
Well, then why'd you bring all these newspapers?
这是四个月前的报纸了 好吧?
They're four months old, okay?
当垫布用的 小傻瓜
We're using them as a drop cloth, dumbass.
好吧 我又不清楚你想怎么刷墙
Well, I don't know all your fancy painting terms,
而且 阿历 这又不是什么大不了的
and besides, Al, it's no big deal.
你应该出去约会才对
You should be out there dating.
精彩的世界像你敞开大门
I mean, the world is open to you.
水瓶座女孩 追求你自己的幸福吧
Chase your joy, dear libra.
什么?
What?
哦 人家正在读你四个月前的星座运势
Oh, I'm just reading your horoscope from four months ago.
这上面还说了 你会遇到一个高个黑人
It also says that you will meet a tall, dark stranger.
Sanjay Gupta医生确实跟我搭讪来着
I did get hit on by Dr. Sanjay Gupta.
Sanjay Gupta医生勾搭你你居然没告诉任何人?
You got hit on by Sanjay Gupta and didn't tell anybody?
是啊
Yeah.
对了 阿历 你和戴夫一起住的时候
Hey, al, when you were living with Dave,
他有没有
did he ever
偷你吃剩的东西 或者拿去丢掉?
steal your leftovers, maybe throw them out?
是有过
It's happening.
有过什么? 你也是同谋吗?
What's happening? Are you part of the conspiracy?
你这么做是因为你觉得我太肥吗?
Are you all doing this because you think I'm chubby?
但我医生说我的身材是因为水份太多撑大的
Because my doctor says that I retain water
就跟生活在潮湿气候的孕妇一样
like a pregnant woman in a humid climate,
这可是一种真正的疾病!
which is a real condition!
马克斯 戴夫爱梦游
Max, Dave is a sleepwalker,
好吧 他会做些怪异的事
okay, and he does crazy things...
吃东西 给花移土
Eating, repotting plants.
他甚至会唱"悲惨世界"里的所有歌
He even sang all the songs from "les mis,"
而且赞爆了!
and he nailed it!
好吧 你跟他说的时候他什么反应?
Well, what did he do when you told him?
他说他从来没有看过"悲惨世界"
Said he had never seen "les mis."
的确很诡异
It was very weird.
那梦游呢?
About the sleepwalking.
哦 矢口否认
Oh. Totally denies it.
我要把他抓个现行
I'm gonna have to catch him in the act.
我得搞台夜视仪...
I'm gonna need night vision goggles...
要高档的 最好是军用级别的
High-end, probably military grade.
得花个九千到一万块吧 你打算给我多少?
Runs about $9,000, $10,000. How much are you paying me?
五十块和一盒芝士兔子
50 bucks and a box of cheddar bunnies.
见鬼 我真的需要这些装备
Damn! I need those things.
听着 你怎么不去问下简 找她借台
Look, why don't you just ask Jane if you can borrow
她的针孔摄像机?
her nanny cam?
简怎么会有针孔摄像机?
Why does Jane have a nanny cam?
因为我想知道我们的员工都在干些什么
Because I like to know what our stuff is doing
我们出去的时候 好吧 一些工人
when we're not here. Okay, we had some workers
我不信任他们 我喜欢泰迪熊
that I didn't trust, and then I just kinda fell in love
所以我把她放这儿了
with the Teddy bear, so I left it there.
这么说你想偷拍布拉德咯?
So you're trying to catch Brad doing something?
是啊 真是见鬼 到现在为止什么都没拍到
Yes, damn it! Why hasn't it worked yet?
嘿 亲爱的!
Hey, honey!
嗨 宝贝
Hi, babe.
希望你的侄女会喜欢泰迪熊
So I hope your niece likes the Teddy bear,
记住 只有八GB的（存储容量）。。。
and just remember, there's only 8 gigabytes...
的拥抱
Of hugs to give.
你们准备录什么?
So what are you trying to film?
神马? 你都知道了?
What? You know about the Teddy cam?
当然了 但是太棒了 我知道怎么利用它
Of course, but it's cool. I learned how to use it
来为我谋福利
to my advantage.
嘿 宝~
Hey, babe.
马克斯找到了家城里最好的牛排馆
Max found this place with the best prime rib in the city.
在脱衣舞夜总会里 但是我向你保证
Now it's in a strip club, but I promise you,
-我只是去吃顿午餐 -当然了 宝贝
- I'm just going there for lunch. - Of course, boo.
哦 我的... 嗯
Oh, my n... Unh.
-为什么不让我说完? -好吧
- Why can't I say it? - Fine.
-我的... -别 我改变想法了
- My n... - Nope. Changed my mind immediately.
好吧 我现在就带着我的泰迪熊搭车
All right. I'm gonna go get on the bus with my Teddy bear,
买一块沙拉三明治 然后把它放冰箱里
buy a falafel sandwich, put it in the fridge,
然后当场抓包梦游的戴夫偷吃我的食物
and catch a sleepwalking Dave eating it.
你说的这些难道都没有让你重新思考一下
Nothing in that sentence makes you want to reassess
你活着是为了什么吗?
what you're doing with your life at all?
-没有 -好吧
- Nope. - All right.
拜 简!
Bye, Jane!
拜! 然后...
Bye! So...
跟卡尔去喝一杯怎么样?
How'd drinks go with Carl?
哦 还不错 卡尔是个好人
Oh, it was cool. Carl's a good guy.
哦 听你这么说我太高兴了
Ohh. I'm so happy, '
因为我真的真的非常喜欢戴安娜
cause I really, really like Dianne,
虽然我不太相信他们说的一些事
although I can't believe all the stuff they've been through.
-什么事? -什么 你还不知道吗?
- What's that now? - What, you don't know?
完整的埃塞俄比亚收养程序
The whole Ethiopian adoption process,
他们是如何捐款给孤儿院的?
how they lost money from a bogus orphanage?
你们俩大男人看比赛的时候都说些什么啊?
What did you guys talk about while you watched the game?
嗯 这些玉米面里面有豆子
Mmm. These nachos have beans in them.
嗯 我大爱豆子
Mmm. I love beans.
听着 他们会成为我们新的夫妻档朋友...
Okay, these are going to be our new good couple friends...
所以 你得向卡尔敞开心扉
Okay, so you need to just open to Carl,
让他也能对你张开怀抱
and let him open up to you.
没错 敞开心扉
Right. Open up.
-好的 -带有感情的 对不对?
- Yeah. - Emotionally, right?
好 够了
Okay. Clean it up.
我就是确认一下
I was just checking.
嘿! 你好吗 布拉德?
Hey! What up, Brad?
手都满了 兄弟
Hands are kinda full, bro.
哦 我看到了 的确是的
Oh. Yeah, they are.
嘿 嗯 卡尔 嗯 简告诉我
Hey, uh, Carl, um, Jane told me
你和戴安娜收养小孩的事
about you and Dianne and the adoption thing.
哦 是啊
Oh, yeah.
如果你想谈点什么的话
If you, like, need to talk about it or anything,
我会成为你聆听的对象...
I could make me be that person who you do that...
毫不犹豫的
Forthwith.
感激不尽
I really appreciate it.
没什么的 老兄
Oh, no problem, bro.
对了
Yeah.
另外戴安娜跟我说了你跟简之间
And Dianne told me about the huge problems
的大问题
you're having with Jane...
就是你们得去婚姻辅导
And that you had to go to couples therapy,
如果你想谈谈 我可以听你诉苦
so if you wanna talk, I'm listening.
对 老兄 听起来不错
Yeah, man. Sounds great, man.
等等 你说谁去了哪儿?
Wait. Uh, who went where now?
老兄 我愿意帮你
Dude, I'm here for ya.
喔
Oh.
我想这比击掌更可笑 对吧?
I guess that's worse than the high five, huh?
好 我们出去再斗 行吧?
All right. Let's be Rambos out there, right?
行 老兄
Yeah, man.
你先 我随后
You're first blood. I'm second blood.
哦 好的
Oh, man.
啊哈 抓住你了戴夫 你这个偷三明治的混蛋
Aha. Gotcha, Dave, you falafel-stealing bastard!
阿历克斯 我说过了我对结伴约会的事很抱歉
Al, I said I was sorry about the double date thing,
但现在是时候找寻点严厉的爱了
but it's time for some tough love.
你知道戴夫约会了很多次 对吧?
You know Dave's been dating a lot, right?
很多很多 像天蝎座一样多
Like, a lot a lot. Like, dicaprio a lot.
说真的 我不在乎
Seriously, I don't care.
他甚至连特蕾西 鲁巴尔斯基也睡过了
He even slept with Tracy lubarsky.
高中那个?这个骚货!
From high school? That slut!
这说得也太难听了点吧
Kinda harsh.
我说的是戴夫
I meant Dave.
戴夫在哪?今天他把他的卡车停这儿了吗?
Where's Dave? Did he park his truck here today?
他开到里格利了 为什么问这个?
He took it down to wrigley. Why?
因为现在我有他从冰箱里偷食物的证据了
Because I now have proof that he's been stealing the food
这也使一个成年男人在公共场合
from the fridge, which makes it okay for a grown man
带泰迪熊说得通了
to carry
如果有人问的话
a Teddy bear in public... If anyone asks.
马克斯 戴夫是不是有过很多约会啊?
Max, has Dave been dating a lot?
严厉的爱
Tough love.
是的 他很火 就像约翰 梅尔那样火
Yeah. He's on fire. Like, John Mayer on fire.
这是指比天蝎座多还是少?
Is that more or less than dicaprio?
多
More.
-哇-是的
- Wow. - Yeah.
-我没意识到...-我知道
- I didn't realize... - I know.
好吧 朋友们 我想我准备好了
Okay. You know what, guys? I think I'm ready.
我准备好重新开始约会了
I am ready to start dating again.
太棒了
That's great.
今晚上在米奇湖有一个单身豪饮船游
There's a singles booze cruise tonight on lake mich.
我们好好发挥
We play our cards right,
我们7点喝完小女生玛格丽塔
we are drunk off skinny girl margaritas by 7:00.
我们9点就能跟投资银行家亲近
We are knee-deep in investment bankers by 9:00!
我要去!哦 是不是没邀请我?
I'm in! Oh, was I not invited?
你是不是跟戴安娜说了
Did you tell Dianne
我们去婚姻辅导那件事了?
we went to couples therapy?
你在说什么啊 小点心?
What are you talking about, biscuit?
不不不 别提小点心 别嘘
No, no, no, no, no. No biscuit. No boo.
别说亲爱的 别提黑帅哥
No sweetie. No black han solo.
没一个你宠物的名字能让你
None of your pet names are
回避这个问题
gonna get you out of this.
现在告诉我你跟她说那事了吗?
Now did you tell her that?
好吧 我说了 但只因为她跟我说了那么多
Okay, I did, but only because she shared so much.
我指的是 我也得向她说点啊
I mean, I had to say something.
但婚姻辅导这事能随便说吗?
Yeah, but couples therapy?
我也不知道
I don't know. Couples therapy.
对吧?咱两?婚姻辅导...这真是...
Right? Us? Couples therapy... That's...
这也太疯狂了
That's crazy.
哦
Ohh.
女士 你做了什么?
Woman, what did you do?
准确的说我们没去
Technically we did not go,
但在阿历克斯和戴夫分手后 我只是
but after Alex and Dave split up, I just...
我吓坏了 我想去见婚姻辅导师
I was so freaked out, I wanted to go see a couples therapist
确保我们很好 所以我想我会见一些
to make sure we were okay, so I thought I'd meet a few,
你知道的 看谁适合
you know, see who fit.
等等 你试了治疗师了?多少个?
Wait. You auditioned therapists? How many?
-五个-五个?
- Five. - Five?
就是五个!瞧 我本认为我们有交流障碍
Five! See, I thought maybe we had trouble communicating,
但第一个治疗师说我们只是交流方式不同
but the first doctor said we just had different styles,
然后接着 第二个治疗师说 我需要
and then, well, the second one said that, you know, I needed
马上提出问题 而且他有口臭
to bring up issues sooner, and he had bad breath,
接着第三个治疗师
and then third one
看起来像个女版斯科特 巴古拉
looked like a female Scott bakula,
这让我压力太大
which just stressed me out,
因为我"人到中年"还落后好多没看
because I am way behind on my "men of a certain age"s,
而且你知道妈妈多么喜欢一个干净的录像机
and you know how mama likes a clean dvr,
接着第四个治疗师问我为什么
and then the fourth one asked me why
去找了这么多治疗师...
I went to so many therapists...
一点都不喜欢他...
Did not like him at all...
接着第五个治疗师让我意识到
And then the fifth one made me realize that
我有一个很棒的老公和一段美好的婚姻
I have an amazing husband and a great marriage,
所以周围一切都很好
so all is good in the neighborhood.
-好 很好-我明白 你很生气
- Good. Great. - Okay, you're mad,
但如果你能敞开心扉
but I wouldn't have had to go to all these therapists
我也用不着非得去找这些治疗师
if I thought that you would be open to it.
哦 那么这是我的错了?行 随便你
Oh, so now it's on me? Okay. All right. Fine.
等一下 你要去哪儿?
Well, wait. Where are you going?
去工作 因为我老婆发疯
To work, because my wife is insane.
我没发疯 行吗?
I am not insane, okay?!
第一 三 五治疗师确定我没疯
Doctors one, three, and five confirmed that!
我们在看什么? 为什么你带着
What are we watching, and why are you carrying around
一只泰迪熊?
a Teddy bear?
别担心莫里熊 他跟着我呢
Don't worry about Murray the bear. He's with me.
另外阿历克斯跟我说了你梦游的事 我愿意
And Alex told me about your sleepwalking. I am willing to
打赌这个录像能证明你偷了该死的食物
bet that this tape proves that you stole the freakin' food.
-她跟你说那个了?-哦 当然
- She told you about that? - Oh, yeah.
老兄 我没梦游!
Dude, I do not sleepwalk!
我不知道为什么每个人...啊!
I don't know why everybody... aah!
-我梦游-嘣!抓到你了
- I sleepwalk. - Boom! Gotcha.
瞧吧 你正要去冰箱那儿
See, you're gonna go to the fridge.
回头你有要去...然后你从冰箱走开
Soon you're gonna go... and you're walking away from the fridge.
-那么谁偷的食物?-我为什么要鞠躬?
- Well, who stole the food then? - And why was I bowing?
等等!停!看见那个了吗?
Wait, wait, wait! Stop! Stop! Did you see that?
哈?倒回去!
Huh? Go back!
-倒回去!-我在倒着呢!
- Go back! - I am. I am going back!
好啊
Okay.
老兄 有人住在我们的天花板上吗?
Dude, is there a guy living in our ceiling?
是的 伙计 有个人住在我们的天花板上
Yes, dude. There's a guy living in our ceiling.
为什么我们要从马克斯那给你的商店弄油漆?
Why are we getting paint for your store from Max's?
他说他有个朋友
He said he had a guy.
马克斯的银行账户是他床下的一个垃圾袋
Max's bank account is a garbage bag under his bed,
但说到他有个涂油漆的朋友
but he's got a paint guy?
完全说得通
Makes total sense.
噢 嘿
Oh. Hey.
嗨 我叫马尔科姆
Hi. I'm Malcolm.
我是 呃 戴夫和马克斯楼上的新邻居
I'm, uh, Dave and Max's new upstairs neighbor.
他们 呃...我没冰箱
They, um... I don't have a fridge,
所以他们说我可以来这儿用他们的
so they said I could come in here and use theirs.
好吧 我叫阿历克斯 她叫彭妮
Well, I'm Alex, and this is penny.
我们事实上只是来拿些油漆
We actually just came to pick up some paint,
很明显不在这儿
which is clearly not here.
哦 有趣 因为我事实上是名画家
Oh, that's funny, 'cause I'm actually a painter.
像拉斐尔或米开朗琪罗那样的?
Like Raphael or Michelangelo?
呃 他们是文艺复兴时的
Well, they were, like, renaissance guys.
-我更像个概念艺术家-像多纳泰罗那样的?
- I'm more of a conceptual artist. - Like donatello?
事实上他是一名雕刻家
Well, he was a sculptor.
好吧 我只知道三个忍者神龟 我还是出局吧
Well, I only know three ninja turtles, so I'm out.
谁是你最喜欢的?
Who was your favorite?
恩...艺术上讲 多纳泰罗
Um... for art, donatello,
论忍者神龟的话 就喜欢拉斐尔了
and for ninja turtling, Raphael all the way.
完全赞同
Totally.
- 阿历克斯能跟你谈一小下吗? - 行?
- Al? Can I talk to you for a skootch? - Yeah? Mm-hmm.
- 怎么了? - 看什么发生了
- What? - See what happens
你放开自己去再次约会了
when you open yourself up to dating again?
- 看机会来了! - 他?真的吗?
- Look what comes along! - Him? Really?
对啊 他很可爱
Yeah. He is cute in,
像一个飞靶射击的乌尔里奇那样
like, a Skeet Ulrich kinda way.
他聪明 懂艺术 约他出去
He's smart. He's artistic. Ask him out.
好吧 他是飞靶射击式的可爱
Okay, he is skeet-cute,
但我不知道该不该
but I don't know.
他是戴夫的邻居...
He's Dave's neighbor...
特蕾西 鲁巴尔斯基（Dave睡了的那个高中放荡女）
Tracy lubarsky.
那么马尔科姆 我不确定
So, Malcolm, I don't know,
今晚想跟我喝一杯吗?
would you like to maybe get a drink tonight?
我们可以深入讨论忍者神龟
We can dive into the whole ninja turtling debate.
- 我来不了 - 哦
- I can't. - Ohh.
我得去今晚的画廊开幕式
Uh, I've got the gallery opening tonight I'm supposed to be at.
嗯 你想跟我一起去吗?
Uh, would you, I don't know, like to come with me?
喔 当然 我喜爱画廊开幕式!
Uh, yeah. I love gallery openings!
酷 你去过很多吗?
Cool. Have you been to many?
呃 像有五 六千
<i>Pfft. Uh... pfft, like, five, six... thousand.</i>
她该在哪跟你碰面?
Where should she meet you?
那就七点半在上西的画廊见吧
Um, say, 7:30 at the gallery on west superior.
听起来真不错 说够了
That sounds super... erior. You're done.
噢 天呐
Oh, my God.
- 拜! - 我说了什么?抱歉啦!
- Bye! - What was that? Sorry!
我约会了
I'm doing it.
噢 天呐 我真为你感到骄傲 他看起来真棒
Oh, my God. I am so proud of you. He seems so great.
只要能找到一个正常的好男人，牺牲什么我都愿意啊
Ohh! What I wouldn't give to find a nice, normal guy.
你这个偷食物的贼马上下来! 你知道
You get down here right now you food thief! You know,
租我这地方的俄罗斯人告诉我这上面
the Russian guy that rented me this place told me there was
有一个能爬行的空间 但我从没费工夫看过
a crawl space up there, but I never even bothered to look.
那是因为你怕蜘蛛 老兄
That's 'cause you're afraid of spiders, dude.
那是我第三大恐惧症
It's my third biggest phobia,
排在公众演讲和没化妆的变装皇后
behind public speaking and drag queens with no makeup.
咱们上去吧
Let's go up there.
我不确定 老兄 这可相当高
I don't know, man. It's pretty high.
快点 是个男人就上来
Come on! Let's be men and get up there!
这实在容易 老兄
It's really easy, dude.
这实在... 喔 天呐
It's really... Oh, God.
好吧 这很难 这很难 这很难
Okay. It's hard. It's hard. It's hard.
我上去了 快来吧!快来快来
I got it. I got it. Come on now! Come on. Come on.
老兄
Dude.
我在走廊发现另一个入口
I found another entrance in the hallway.
那儿有楼梯 走那儿比较容易
It had stairs. Way easier.
哇 这地方没我想象的那样恐怖
Wow. This place is not as creepy as I thought it was gonna be.
我想把他的擦脸油都挤到他的篮子里
I totally thought I was gonna be putting the lotion
但这家伙衬衫的品味还真不错
in the basket, but this guy's got pretty good taste in shirts.
他其实是个很棒的艺术家
He's actually a pretty good artist.
你完全能从画中人的表情就感受到他们的痛苦
You can totally see the pain on this guy's face.
哦 老天
Oh, my God.
他拿了我们的苹果脆片 他不能再拿了
He took our apple smacks! This has gotta stop.
我们要呆在这直到这大混蛋...
We are staying here until this bastard...
喔 天呐
Oh, my God!
这是我见过的最大的蜘蛛
That is the biggest spider I've ever seen!
哦 我的错 这只是一个电线球
Oh. My bad. It's just a ball of wire.
戴夫?
Dave?
嘿! 波拉德!怎么了 伙计?
Hey! "B"-rad! What's wrong, man?
你在那个会上太安静了
You were so quiet in that meeting.
我的意思是
I mean,
你连在彼得森以他经典的o.J. 形象
you didn't even laugh when Peterson whipped out
冲出去的时候都没笑
his classic o.J. Impression.
经典的彼得森
Classic Peterson.
对吧?哦 老兄 我爱那形象
Right? Oh, man. I love that impression.
- 是的 - 嗯
- Yeah. - Mm.
我能跟你坦诚点儿事吗?
Can I bounce something off you?
我就像一个弹簧垫 兄弟 随你坦诚
I'm a trampoline, bro. Bounce whatever you want.
呃 简单独去的婚姻辅导
Uh, Jane went to couples therapy without me,
而且她不认为我能接受 但那不是重点
and she didn't think I'd be open to it, but that's not the point.
我只是不认为我们之间真的有问题
I-I just don't think we have real problems.
你们或许没有
You probably don't.
女人们 她们脑袋中有一个生产问题的工厂
Women... they got a problem factory up here,
但 就像所说的那样 你得让她知道
but, uh, that being said, you gotta let her know
那样她有忧虑就可以跟你说
that she can talk to you if she has concerns.
我指的是 婚姻是条双行道
I mean, marriage is a 2-way street.
你说得对 谢谢 老兄
You're right. Thanks, man.
不客气...
No problemo...
先生(西班牙语)
Senor.
谢谢(西班牙语)
Gracias.
你知道吗 老兄?
You know what, man?
这种关系很不错
This right here... This is nice.
听着 既然说道这里 嗯...
Look, uh, now that I've got your ear, um...
我有点事情想跟你分享下
I've been meaning to share something with you.
好啊 朋友
All right, man.
分享吧 兄弟 我是分享协会的董事长
<i>Share it up, dude. I am the shareman of the board.</i>
额...戴安娜和我...
Uh... Dianne and I...
我们最近有点问题...
We've been having some problems...
很抱歉听到你这么说
I'm sorry about that, man.
关于找个人来分享我们的床
Finding someone to share our bed with us.
额...你是说...
Uh... like...
宠物狗吗?
Like a... like a dog?
说不定真有根狗绳子哦（指SM）
There will probably be a leash involved.
是吧?
Right?
听起来有点怪 真的好怪啊
That got weird. That got so weird.
- 我知道 是吧? - 整个事都好怪了
- I know, huh? - This whole thing's weird.
- 你好棒 - 你... 噢噢
- You're great. - You're... ooh. Ooh.
- 噢 是啊 - 噢
- Ohh. Yeah. - Ohh.
嘿 呆子们 我有大新闻
Hey, nerds. I got huge news.
好的 戴夫 我真的希望
Okay, Dave, I really hope
你可以成熟的看待这件事情
you can be mature about this.
我可能终于逼阿历克斯去
So I may have pushed Alex to go
她的"落跑新娘"之后的
on her first date
第一次约会哦
post-the whole non-wedding thing.
你介意不?
Are you cool with that?
当然 我完全不在乎
Yeah. I'm totally cool with that.
你确定吗 兄弟?这个对你应该有点难
Are you sure, dude? It's gotta be kinda tough.
有点难 不 完全无所谓的好伐
It's gotta be kinda tough. No, it's totally easy for me.
- 他帅不帅?成功人士?- 恩 不重要
- Is he handsome? Successful? - Eh, it doesn't matter.
- 他高不高? - 其实他是你邻居
- Is he tall? - He's actually your neighbor.
比较可爱 乱乱的那种男人 他说他住在楼上
He's that kinda cute, scruffy guy. He said he lived upstairs.
你们之前把他藏在哪里了?
Where have you been hiding him?
噢 我的天 我干什么了?
Oh, my God. What have I done?
让阿历克斯去约一个擅自住在别人家里的游民
Set up Alex with a homeless squatter.
一个无家可归的治安维持会游民
A homeless vigilante squatter.
我们要去阻止约会
We have to stop this.
- 嗨 - 听着 我很抱歉
- Hi. - Listen, I'm sorry.
我不应该指责你缺乏交流
I shouldn't accuse you of not communicating
而同时又不给你交流的机会
when I don't give you a chance to.
没事了 宝贝 我也抱歉 我应该让你更清楚
It's okay, babe. I'm sorry, too. I need to be better at letting
的了解你永远可以跟我交流
you know you can always talk to me.
哦 我爱我唯一的黑帅哥
Ohh. I love my black han solo.
哦 而且我还要谢谢你督促我向卡尔敞开心扉
Oh, and thank you for pushing me to open up to Carl.
他向我敞开心扉 然后我们都感觉非常好
He opened up to me, and we got to a really great place.
看 我就知道我们可以
See, I knew we could
从卡尔和戴安娜身上学习很多东西
learn a lot from Carl and Dianne.
是啊 哦 是啊 我们学习了很多
Yeah. Oh, yeah. We learned a lot,
而且他们有这么多事情可以教我们 比如
and they have so much more to teach us, like...
哦 说曹操曹操到 ... 嗨！ 嗨！
Oh, speaking of which... Hi! Hi!
嗨
Hey.
我真高兴你和布拉德相处的那么好
I am so glad that you and Brad are clicking,
因为我真的非常喜欢你们
'cause I really like you guys.
哦 我们也好喜欢你哦 简 非常喜欢哦
Oh, we like you, too, Jane... a lot.
我-我更喜欢你们了
I-I like you even more!
哦 那很棒
Well, that's great.
那好 你看 我们三个现在到对面街去
Well, what do you say the three of us go across the street,
登记一个旅馆 刮刮干净
check into a hotel, shave down,
然后交给我们的身体来说话 咋样?
and let our bodies do the talking, huh?
听起来是不是很有意思?
Wouldn't that be so fun?
不 真的 我们想和你爱爱
No, seriously. We want to have sex with you.
哦 我的上帝  真疯狂
Oh, my God. That was insane.
他们真的想要探索我的阴道
They legitimately wanted to get down with my va-Jay-na.
你有什么好抱怨的?他们居然木有邀请我
What are you complaining about? I didn't even get invited.
但是你必须承认 他们是很开放的一对
But you gotta admit, they are a very open couple.
好吧 我活该
Okay, I deserve that.
你看 我很高兴你让我敞开心扉
Look, I'm happy you got me to open up,
但是从现在开始
but from now on,
不再和一些诡异的人或者是
instead of doing it with creepy guys at work
长的像斯科特 巴古拉的心理咨询师
or therapists that look like Scott bakula,
让我们一起敞开心扉
let's just do it together.
对 而且我们要回到和正常的朋友一起约会
Yes, and we can also go back to hanging out with our normal friends...
感谢上帝
Thank goodness.
他们正在去阻止阿历克斯
Who are apparently on their way to stop Alex
和一个住在马克斯和戴夫天花板上的人约会
from dating some guy who lives in Max and Dave's ceiling.
我喜欢那些疯狂的孩子
I love those crazy kids.
阿历克斯!等等!你不能和这个人约会
Alex! Wait! You can't date this guy.
- 你干哈呢? - 我在阻止你犯一个
- What are you doing? - I'm stopping you from making
严重的错误
a big mistake.
什么?你可以和半个芝加哥的女人约会
What? You get to date half of Chicago.
顺带，那个特蕾西 鲁巴尔斯基?我吐
Tracy Lubarsky, by the way? Ew!
而我好不容易约会一次 你却来搞破坏?
And I finally go on one date, and you want to show up and ruin it?
阿历 斯基特乌尔里奇住在
Al, Skeet Ulrich lives in
马克斯和戴夫的天花板上
Max and Dave's ceiling.
等等 你们是马克斯和戴夫
Wait. You're Max and Dave.
是啊
Yeah.
对头 而且你不应该拿属于别人的苹果片麦片
That's right, and you do not take someone's apple smacks
还不被打扁 孙子！
without getting a serious beat-down, son!
兄弟 你说水果麦片的时候装狠是吓不到人的
Dude, you can't act hard when you're talking about fruit cereal.
是吗 那如果我做对他
Yeah? What if I
做一些警告突进动作呢 啊?
do a couple warning lunges at him, huh?
神经病眨眼 怎么样?
Some maniac blinks, huh?!
来啊 围巾男!
Let's dance, scarf man!
我这下完全搞不懂了
I am so lost.
哦 我的 我的朋友告诉我那个地方
Uh, my... my friend told me about this space,
我只是在那里住到我卖出去第一幅画
and I was only living there until I sold a painting,
但是我从来没有见到过戴夫和马克斯
but I had never actually seen Dave and Max,
只是听到他们呢
just heard them.
- 等等 你是爱丽丝! - 谁是爱丽丝?
- Wait. You're Alice! - Who's Alice?
Dave失恋后哭哭啼啼了好几天
Oh, Dave mourned the end of the relationship for days.
我以为他在说"爱丽丝" 但是听的不是很清楚
I thought he was saying "Alice, " but it was hard to hear
- 因为啜泣声 - 啜泣?
- through all the sobbing. - Sobbing?
不不 你没有...
No, no. You didn't...
你没听见我啜泣，我一点都不在乎的
You heard me not sobbing and being totally over it.
- 这话什么意思? - 我回头告诉你
- What does that sound like? - I'll tell you later!
那就是为什么我把
That's why
那系列画称作"戴夫的绝望"
I called the series "Dave's despair."
我说那些画里面的痛苦表情看起来这么眼熟
I thought the emotional pain in those paintings looked familiar.
伙计 你是个超级有才华的艺术家
You're a super-talented artist, man...
但是你还是不能偷别人的东西！
But you do not steal from people!
你说的对 我很抱歉 你穿的是我的衬衫吗?
You're right. I'm sorry. Is that my shirt?
什么?这个真是...
What? That is just...
我要从礼品店那里出去
I'm gonna exit through the gift shop.
等等 你蜗居在他们夹层里面?
Wait. So you squat in their crawl space?
嗨 我是个叛逆者 而且我知道你喜欢这型的
Hey, I'm a rebel, and you dig it, I know,
但是我-我觉得我们不应该再约会下去了
but I-I don't think we should see each other anymore.
兄弟法规不允许的 我不能这样对他
There's a bro code, and I can't do that to him.
对不起 孩子
Sorry, kid.
唔
Mm.
有没有搞错?
What?
所以..看来明显某人是想来告诉我
So... clearly someone is trying to tell me
我还没有准备好约会
that I am not ready to date yet.
恩，顺带，我知道我没权利这么说
Oh, by the way, and I know I don't have a say in it...
但是如果你准备好了，我保证
But when you're ready, I promise...
我会冷静对待的
I'll be cool with it.
谢谢
Thank you.
事实上 有个住在我们牛扒车下面的伙计
In fact, there's a guy living under my steak truck.
我可以给你们两个介绍介绍
I could introduce the two of you.
- 他有很不错的络腮胡子 -滚蛋
- He's got a nice, full beard. - Stop it.
兄弟 你和
Dude, what is going on with you
这些冰桃茶怎么了?
and all this diet peach iced tea?
哦 这个不是给我们的 马尔科姆 接着啊
Oh, this isn't for us. Malcolm! Incoming!
嗨 谢谢 兄弟 希望你喜欢这个衬衫
Hey! Thanks, man! Enjoy the shirt!
酷 哦 嗨 有没有皮带...
Cool. Oh, hey, do you have a belt I could...
你有没有..一个棕色的会比较...
Do you have... A brown one would be...
来了
Comin' at ya.
这家伙真心棒
This guy's awesome.
女士们 先生们 阿历克斯
Ladies, gentlemen, Alex,
我称它为"睡Dave的故事"
I like to call this "the legend of sleepy Dave."
欣赏吧
Enjoy.
哇噢
Wow.
哦 我都不知道我会做那个
Oh, that's a skill I didn't know I had.
真是杯具
This is sad.
不会吧 你那是在测你的脉搏吗
What, are you checking your pulse right there?
你现实中从来不慢跑
You never jog in real life.
- 嗨 身材不错 - 身材真好
- Hey, pretty good form. - That's really good form.
边俯卧撑边吃饼干?强悍
Cookies with a push-up? Bold.
好的 哦 现在这个是...
All right. Oh! Now this is...
这个真是精心的杰作啊 戴夫
This is a tour de force, Dave.
这个会有性感的吗
Is it gonna get sexy?
恩 这里开始变得性感
Yeah, it gets sexy right here.
好国王温萨斯勒斯向外看去
Good king wenceslas looked out
看到史蒂芬的盛宴
on the feast of Stephen
当雪花迂回飘下
when the snow lay roundabout
深深的松脆的均匀的
deep and crisp and even